

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER

# **CHRISTIAN A.SANCHEZ**

## **GET IN CONTACT**

Home: 04-504-4086 Mobile: 096-3787611 Mail: christianabrahamsanchez@gmail.com GitHub: Chrisnewgear (github.com) Web: https://christiansanchezcv.netlify.app Netlify: https://app.netlify.com/teams/chrisnewgear/overview

Current address: Cdla. Colinas de la Alborada Mz. 726 V. 18

## **PERSONAL PROFILE**

I'm a autodidact Junior Frontend Developer with 1 year of experience, with skills in interactive design with 3 years of experience. I am also passionate and willing to learn new technologies to enhance my skills in coding and design, furthermore I'm studying software developing career at "Tecnológico Universitario ARGOS".

## **AREAS OF EXPERTISE**

- HTML, CSS, SQL, JavaScript, jQuery, Git, GitHub, Debian based Linux Distros. Materialize, OOP.
- Basic knowledge of PHP, JAVA,
  C, C++, React, Design Systems.
- Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere Pro, Adobe XD, Figma
- PCs, laptops & Mac repairing.

## **OTHER SKILLS**

- The ability to analyze complex technical information
- · Detail oriented
- · Excellent problem solver
- Drawing & Illustration
- · Soft skills
- English C1 level

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### ALTURA

SQL Administrator(Currently)

- SQL DBs management
- · Frontend developer

## TEDU (AGRICULTORES DEL ECUADOR)

Frontend Developer 2021 - 2022)

- Frontend developer
- · Technical support & consulting

#### UTFG

Clerk | 2019-2020

- Customer service
- · Technical support

#### **BANCO GUAYAQUIL**

Senior Assistant | 2005 - 2016

- Document digitalization department
- · Clearing house
- Legal requirements
- · Technical support

## **EDUCATION HISTORY**

## ESCUELA POLITÉCNICA DEL LITORAL

System Analyst, 2005-2006 (Dropped out)

## TECNOLÓGICO UNIVERSITARIO ARGOS

Software Development (Currently)

## **SELF-TOUGHT LEARNING**

#### **UDEMY**

Web Development with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, AJAX, PHP, SQL.

#### ΡΙ ΔΤ7Ι

- Software Development School (Currently)
- Web Development School (Currently)

#### **OPEN BOOTCAMP**

• Frontend Development (Currently)